what's up everybody my name is kina and
once again i'm waiting on a late amazon
delivery
if you've had this experience stick
around and i'll show you the best way
to get compensated for your late
deliveries let's start the video
okay these tips might not actually take
you to the moon but they will add up
especially if late deliveries are a
common occurrence in your household it
can be frustrating shelling out 120
each year for fast amazon prime
deliveries
only to be stuck waiting for an
important package pretty much anybody
who's used prime for any significant
period of time
has had this frustrating experience i
certainly have
and personally for most deliveries it
really doesn't matter a day or two of
waiting is okay
but every once in a while i really need
the item that day
and that's when i get bothered in the
past i've successfully gotten
three different types of compensation by
reaching out to amazon via their chat
feature online
amazon used to extend your prime
membership by a month for reaching out
and asking every time there's a late
package
and i would regularly get four to six
free months
of the service just by reaching out so
18 months instead of 12.
and while this policy has been
discontinued you can still get 10
amazon credits just by asking and you
can potentially get more than 10
if the item is large or expensive and
you can also potentially get a full
refund of the item
but i've been rejected and your mileage
may vary it's still worth a shot though
so let's get into how to do this the
first thing you should do whenever a
package is late
is load amazon.com
then type contact us into the search bar
then click the contact us button and
click start chatting now
you can also find this page by googling
contact amazon i recommend doing this
before the package arrives at your house
as your chances of getting a full refund
and getting to keep the item
increase this way the system might
automatically know which order you're
inquiring about
especially if you reach out quickly as
amazon did here
but if not the amazon robot assistant
should give you the option to select the
order
from a list of your recent purchases
you'll need to click through some of the
automated questions
and then you'll be connected through to
a live agent in this case
you can see that i waited until after my
order was delivered
to reach out
from here you have two options you can
either ask for a full refund
or for compensation personally if i'm
really annoyed
i'll ask for a refund and this has
worked before usually i do this before
the order arrives
because i'm frustrated and if the amazon
agent grants my request
i'll get my money back and the item will
usually show up a day or two later i've
done this successfully
after the package has arrived as well
but anecdotally i've also been rejected
more
when i wait for the delivery typically
they ask if i just want to send it back
for a refund
so your mileage may vary here if you
scroll down and look at the video
description
i've included two different scripts that
you can choose from just copy and paste
them into the chat
in this case you can see them providing
the agent with the order number which i
copied from the order page
and this is usually unnecessary because
you specify earlier in the chat which
order you're inquiring about
but i find sometimes it helps to speed
up the process
now i'm pasting in the exact script
that's included in the description
and i assume that she's going to give me
a 10 account credit
personally i always like to be very
polite and ask about the agent's day
i know that they're probably crammed in
a cube dealing with annoyed people all
day
so i try to be a little ray of sunshine
give it another minute or two and you
can see
that they issue a 10 credit easy
that's about it if you'd like to go for
the full refund option there's a script
in the description below
and try to do it before the item arrives
i haven't always been successful with
this approach
but there's no harm in trying and you
can just go for the 10
credit if it fails i dug through my chat
history and i found this example from
last fall
when i was able to get a full refund in
any case if you found this video useful
please smash the like button i put a lot
of work into each video
and it really helps me when you do that
so thank you all and i'll see you in the
next one
you